I'm about to interview one
of the richest men in Dubai,
and I don't think people truly understand what that means.
Sir, is this your Bugatti?
Yes, it is.
How did you get a Bugatti?
I'm one of the biggest
real estate developers in the world.
What was the most amount of money
that you've made in a single year?
A lot.
Give me a range.
Off the top of my head,
I would say almost $5 billion.
$5 billion.
This is Dubai, a city where billion-dollar deals
are made over coffee, where entire skylines are built
by a single man's vision, and where wealth operates
on a completely different level.
I just flew 16 hours across the world
to be here for this moment.
Today, I'm meeting up with Mohamed Benghadi,
one of the biggest real estate developers
in the entire world, the man behind some
of the most iconic towers on the planet,
to find out how he built a real estate empire
in one of the most competitive cities on Earth.
I'm gonna be going inside the mind of a billionaire
to figure out what it really takes
to build generational wealth at the highest level.
So with that being said,
it's time to go meet Mohamed Benghadi.
All right, you guys, we are
in route right now to interview,
like I said, one of the richest men in Dubai,
Mohamed Benghadi, okay?
And we're gonna be interviewing him not just anywhere,
but at one of the buildings that he built,
the Bugatti Residences.
This guy transformed the entire Dubai skyline.
He built the first Mercedes-Benz Residences in the world.
He built the first Jacob
& Co. Residence in the world.
And now, look at where we are,
the first Bugatti Residence in the world.
This is Mohamed Benghadi.
All right, you guys, look at this right here.
This is the first Bugatti Residence in the world.
This is the first Bugatti Residences, man.
Hey, where are we at right now?
No, we're in Bugatti Residence.
Who are we about to interview?
Mr. Mohamed.
He's one of the biggest developers in the world.
Yes, yes, of course.
First of all, look at the skyline right here.
I want to point this out.
That's the tallest building in the world, the Burj Khalifa.
But man, we're about to interview an absolute legend
and icon out here, you guys.
So let's go meet up with him himself, man.
Come on.
I mean, this has potential to be insane.
What's going on, man?
How are you?
Great to see you, man.
Good to see you.
It's good to see you.
We were letting them know, man,
this is one of your creations right here.
It is.
Where are we at right now?
Bugatti Residences.
And this is the first Bugatti Residence in the world.
The first and only.
Before, you know, I want to ask you some questions.
What goes into that?
I mean, you partnered up with one of the biggest,
most renowned, most credible companies in the world.
How is that even possible?
I mean, I think there's a
lot of passion that goes into that.
You've got to be obsessed.
Obsessed with everything you do, you know.
Wake up every day obsessed with your goals,
obsessed with what you want to achieve in life,
and literally grind.
Growing up, did you think that this was possible?
That you were going to, you know,
have your name on the wall?
On the side of the buildings,
working with some of the biggest companies in the world.
I mean, literally putting up their skyscrapers.
You know, it's funny you ask,
because I had a lot
of Bugatti posters in my room,
being a kid,
but I would have never dreamed to
actually achieve something like this any day.
That's amazing, man.
And, you know, we flew 16 hours out here,
and we want to make this a masterclass
for the younger generation,
trying to become billionaires,
trying to become the best entrepreneurs they can be.
Can we make that happen?
Sure.
So, I got to ask you,
where are you from originally?
From the UAE.
And you never left?
No.
Why not?
I mean, it's the best place in the world, right?
Why is this the best city for business owners?
I think it's the entrepreneurial flair of the city.
I think, you know,
the leadership have been very supportive
in creating this atmosphere
that supports any entrepreneur
in building a billion-dollar business.
And when you were starting out in the business,
were there a lot of no's?
Did you have any failures?
Were there a lot of downsides?
Plenty.
I've had a lot of no's in my life.
Like you said,
you didn't take no for the answer.
I mean, I think the more and more successful
you become in life,
the more you realize that
you're going to fail a lot,
and you're going to get a lot of rejection.
And part of becoming successful
is that maturity of your mindset,
that understanding that you're not always
going to get the answer you want,
and then you've got to navigate
towards the answer you want.
Why was real estate your vehicle?
Because you could have been in any business.
Why do you like real estate as your vehicle
to wealth creation and business building?
Well, I mean, real estate is ultimately
what any wealthy person ends up doing in the end,
I believe.
You know, everyone who makes a lot of money
ends up buying real estate.
Why is that?
Why do the wealthiest,
the most successful people in the world,
why do they all invest in real estate?
I mean, I think as an asset,
it's very...
solid.
You can touch it,
you can feel it,
see it,
smell it.
And I think it's the least volatile.
So in terms of risk management,
you know,
it's always a safe investment.
So I think it's the most versatile asset class
or one of the most out there.
Did you ever diversify?
I did,
but then I learned a very tough lesson
that diversification doesn't always mean
to venture into another sector.
You can always do it in one sector.
And that's the vertical integration.
Absolutely.
That's what we did.
You know,
we became completely vertically integrated
as a developer.
We built a full construction company,
you know,
a factory.
We have seven factories
for joinery,
aluminum,
steel.
And so we really focus on
serving this one
sort of single monstrosity
of a business
rather than,
you know,
getting distracted in different sectors.
So we're about to see the building right here,
but I wanted you to touch on real quick
your progression
of that vertical integration.
When you started out
in the real estate business,
were you selling properties?
Were you brokering?
Like before you had the factories,
before you had the steel manufacturing
and whatnot,
how did you come about,
you know,
kind of obtaining
all the different verticals?
This is something I learned
in business in general.
You never have...
You never have the full picture
from day one.
You just got to start
and navigate your way through.
And, you know,
one of the best quotes
I like about this
is in the book
of His Highness Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum,
the ruler of Dubai.
And he says,
when a bee starts its day,
it doesn't know its full plan.
It just, you know,
leaves and starts harvesting,
you know,
the honey.
And same thing with birds.
And I think, you know,
you never have a plan
that's fully perfect
from day one.
You just start
and you navigate your way through
and you learn,
you fail,
you fix,
and ultimately
you figure out a way.
When you're thrown in the ocean
in a stormy day,
you either drown
or you swim.
Now, there's been a lot of
Day in the Lives on YouTube
where people go
and spend the day
with people at their homes,
their apartments.
We are at an apartment complex
that you're building.
Correct.
This is going to be fascinating.
Can you go show us around
real quick?
Please.
Let's go check it out.
And real quick,
you know what I love?
You got the Bugatti right there
with the Bugatti building right here.
It would be inappropriate
to drive a different car.
I love that.
Let's check it out.
Guys, I can't believe
where Dubai right now.
But I need you to listen
very carefully.
Look, I built
the craziest network
in the entire world
of millionaires.
And billionaires
at just 23 years old.
And it is the only reason
why I've been able to build
a multi-million dollar business
so young.
And for Christmas this year,
I'm doing something insane for you.
I'm opening up
my entire billionaire network
and I'm giving you
direct access to them.
All the millionaires
and the billionaires
that you guys watch me interview,
now I'm letting you
get mentored by them
every single week.
Seriously, guys.
In 2026,
I will be hosting
a live call
with a millionaire
or billionaire mentor
every single week.
You will be able to hop
on Zoom with me
and ask them
your questions live.
It's called
The School of Mentors.
The number one
mentorship network
in the world
for entrepreneurs.
And for Christmas,
if you join
The School of Mentors,
you get three insane bonuses
and a crazy giveaway.
Bonus number one,
you will be able
to get access
to The School of Mentors
for 40% off for life.
Bonus number two,
you can join
for 30 days risk-free.
Seriously,
if you don't love it,
just send us a message
within 30 days
and we'll give you a refund.
Meaning you can literally
join for free
and bonus number three,
you are literally
going to get access
to the recordings
from Billionaire Day 1,
Billionaire Day 2,
Wealth and Investing Day,
AI Day,
and Viral Content Day.
These are private trainings
we hosted with billionaires
and we've never
shared them publicly.
And on top of all that,
five people
who join for this
Christmas special
will be given
lifetime access
to The School of Mentors
for free.
So if you went in,
stop what you're doing right now.
Click the link
in the description
in this video
and grab your spot
before the end of the year.
Because after this,
this Christmas special
will be gone
forever.
So I can't wait
to see you on the inside.
With that being said,
let's get back to the video.
You can see that
they're starting to put
the steel cladding on top.
It's 13 kilometers
of steel cladding
going on the exterior.
So how much goes into
building an apartment
complex like this?
Honestly,
the sort of real estate
you're looking at here
and the sort of people
who have bought it here,
you have the
Crown Penthouse
which is a triplex
that is almost
50,000 square feet.
It has a cinema,
it has a cigar lounge,
it has anything
you can think of.
We have a beach up here,
literally,
a French Riviera
inspired beach.
That's never been done before.
No, it's...
We literally have
two car elevators
to take your Bugatti
into your penthouse,
park it in front of your office
and work from home
looking at your car.
Is it a requirement
that in order to live here
you have to have a Bugatti?
Well, I mean,
I'd like to think
you would have one
if you're buying here.
But I think ultimately
this is for everyone
who appreciates things
that are finer in life.
We have very interesting
clients who have bought
Neymar Jr. footballer.
He bought one here.
Andrea Bocelli.
So,
yeah, very interesting names.
You're known as one of the
fastest developers in the region.
Correct.
What's the secret to that speed?
I think, again,
it goes back to the
vertical integration.
We have our own workforce
all in-house.
We have our factories.
So, like,
these construction companies,
do you own the companies
or are they contracts?
Yes, we do.
Everything, literally.
Everything that goes into
building the product,
we control and we own.
And ultimately,
what that gives you
is agility when it comes
to speed, quality
and cost, obviously.
Did you kind of acquire
these companies
or did you start them
from the ground up?
Mostly started from the ground up.
Some acquired, actually.
So, some opportunities
seen here and there,
you know, steel factory,
acquire it, upgrade it
and ultimately supports you
in building much faster.
Fascinating.
So, what number building
is this for you?
I think you've done
how many, 60 complexes
or something?
A little bit closer to 100.
100 complexes, man?
Yeah.
What's the biggest thing
that you've changed
since the very beginning?
I would imagine
the first one wasn't super easy.
Absolutely.
I think the biggest lesson
I learned when building
these complexes
is focusing on quality
and letting the product
talk for itself.
So, we do a lot of marketing,
of course, as a brand,
you know,
on a global scale.
But I think the best companies
out there worldwide
are the companies
that have products
that market themselves.
You don't need to say anything.
The product speaks for itself.
You have the architect background.
Yes.
Do you have a lot of input
in the design process
for the building?
Oh, I'm always on site.
Are you actually?
Probably more than
the time I spend in office.
Oh, my goodness.
I love it.
Lobby space, you can see.
Monumental height.
It's a very large lobby space.
How many stories
is this one going to be?
This is going to be 46 stories.
We have 180 units here.
And each and every unit
is a piece unique.
Yeah.
So, differently,
layout,
different interior design scheme,
completely bespoke.
What's the average price point
of one of these units?
Well, I mean,
penthouse up there
was listed at 750 million dirhams.
It's just above 200 million dollars.
Oh, my goodness.
Yeah.
And somebody bought it?
Well, we're on the market right now.
Maybe you'll hear some news
someday.
I'm excited to hear it, man.
When you're driving
on the road,
the highway out here in Dubai,
and you look to your right
and your left
and you see your name
on the side of that building,
what does that feeling mean to you?
It makes me feel happy and proud.
But ultimately,
if anything,
it evokes a sense of...
Oh, yeah.
There's an urgency in me
to achieve more.
I mean, comfort is
the most dangerous drug.
You've got to learn
to be comfortable
being uncomfortable
because the moment
you become complacent
and comfortable
is the moment
you have no drive
to achieve more success in life.
So, anything else in here
that we should check out?
Yeah, I mean,
feel free.
What's an underrated thing
at all of your properties
that you have
that a lot of people
don't put enough emphasis on?
I think it's the design.
The design.
Yeah.
I mean,
we put a lot of passion
into our design.
What goes into a great design?
I heard somebody
tell me one time
that in real estate,
it's never a money problem.
It's a creativity problem.
And in your case, right,
you've got some of the most
uniquely designed buildings
that have filled up
and they're renowned out here.
What goes into
your creative process?
I think a lot of storytelling
goes into it.
I think a lot of brand narrative.
It even stems to things
like the name of the project.
You know,
does the name reflect
the architecture?
Does it help
with telling the story?
What sort of elements
are you including
in the interiors,
in the exterior,
in the amenities?
You know,
what lifestyle
are you building?
Is this for people
who are interested
in things like health,
in fitness?
And so,
you build this whole narrative
targeting a specific audience
that you like
to enjoy this product
and see the value.
That's what good design
is about.
Another thing I wanted
to ask you
was about people.
What do you look for
in people
when you're building a business?
One of my favorite quotes,
I think,
was by the CEO of Blackstone.
He said,
every organization
has six out of tens,
seven out of tens,
eight out of tens.
And then he's like,
if you want to build
something truly great,
you've got to focus
on having nines out of tens
and tens out of tens only.
Eight players.
Absolutely.
And he said,
the difference between
an eight out of ten
and a ten out of ten
is huge.
What is that difference
that you see most of the time
that separates an eight
from a ten?
If I have to tell them
what to do,
they're not in the right place.
Do that one.
Say that again.
If I have to tell someone
what to do
or how to do their job,
they're not in the right place.
So let's talk about this
real quick.
Our company has up to
about 50 or so employees now.
We're doing a million
a month right now.
Come on, man.
Let's go.
I'm trying to get like you.
But one of the biggest things
that we see
in the most talented people,
even within our organization,
is they're self-starters.
Oh, yeah.
They go out
and get it themselves.
Oh, yeah.
But they got to think
of new things to do, you know?
We have a saying in Arabic.
We say,
once the chick is born
from the egg,
it knows how to walk.
Or once the duckling is born,
it knows how to swim.
So a person who is good
at what they do
should know what to do
without you telling them
what to do.
And they should be
way better than you
as their boss
to show you
how something should be done.
A lot of people talk about
micromanagement
and how it's bad
and everything.
I don't believe in micromanagement.
I believe in passion management.
So if you're involved
in everything, it's okay.
But as long as
you're empowering people
who are specialized
in something
and know more than you,
you're letting them play
and you're letting them
do their thing
and take your product
to a whole other level
or your company,
you want to bring
those sort of people
into your business.
I love that.
I heard a term one time
and it's always stuck with me.
I interviewed the founder
of LinkedIn, Reid Hoffman.
He sold LinkedIn
to Microsoft
for $26 billion.
And I asked him,
Reid, if you had to start
from zero
and you had one year
to make a billion dollars
in your life
dependent on it,
what would you do?
And he stopped me.
He goes,
I never play a one-year game.
I only play a 10-year game.
What is your mindset
and long-term vision
and thought process
like for your company
and what you're building today?
What are you thinking?
It's definitely long-term.
For me, there's no set term.
It's like till the day I die.
And it's just part
of your lifestyle.
You get used to it.
It's almost like
if you're an athlete
and you're working out,
you don't think
I'm going to work out
for 10 years in my life
and then I'm going to stop
because my body is good now.
It's just part of your lifestyle
and it becomes part
of your daily routine,
your grind every day.
And once you approach
work like that,
you build consistency.
And I think in my mind,
consistency is the most
important ingredient
towards success.
There are a lot of
smart people out there
who haven't made it
and a lot of less smart people
who are more consistent
who have made it.
So I think consistency
plays a big role
in being successful.
See students,
they run the world.
Absolutely.
But yeah, I think it's about
being able to fail,
fall,
and get up every time
and just continue
like nothing happened.
And I think it's successful
people that are like that.
At 31,
if you lost everything tomorrow,
could you make it back?
Absolutely.
What would you do?
Just start again.
And all the lessons I learned.
Do you think
because once it's in you,
it's always in you
once you kind of know
the formula
and how to do it?
Yeah.
You understand the process
so you know
that it's okay to fail.
Being an entrepreneur,
you're going to fail every day.
Even when you are successful,
there's one thing
you're not going to get
fully right.
Secret recipe to success
is try,
fail,
learn,
fix,
try again.
Five steps.
Love it.
The five steps.
So like I said,
outside of one of your creations,
man,
first of all,
congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Hey, and I know you hear it,
but I'm proud of you, man.
You inspire my team
and we've traveled the world.
We've interviewed
over 30 billionaires
and you're hands down
one of the most
one of our favorite people
that we've ever met.
Thank you very much.
And likewise,
I'm proud of you guys
and what you do.
I've been following you
on social media
and you're doing
an amazing job.
Yeah.
Mohamed,
I'm going to ask you,
if me and you died tomorrow
and you had one last message
to leave with the younger generation,
what would that be?
I think it's to leave
something valuable behind,
whether it's a project,
a product,
something that changes
people's lives positively
whilst, you know,
making money for you.
And I think the most
successful companies worldwide
do that exactly.
So I think if you're able
to solve a big problem,
that's what you want to do.
That's what you want
to leave behind.
And ultimately,
that becomes your legacy.
When I last interviewed you,
I learned that
one of your secrets to success
was your belief
and your faith in God.
You said that you've seen
miracles happen in your life.
Yes.
How do you rely on your faith
when times get tough?
There has to be
a master architect
to design all of this,
you know,
the sun and the moon
and everything.
And us, man.
And us, you know.
Humans, you know,
with two cameras in our face
and a microphone.
But ultimately,
I think back to miracles,
I asked for miracles
in my life.
And I think it's
when you're so hopeless
and you reach that point
where you know
you've done everything
you could have done,
but you're still failing.
And then ultimately,
one of those follow-ups
that you thought
would never end up
being a deal
or a successful milestone
suddenly becomes
a breakthrough.
And you had asked for that
in a prayer.
So that makes you believe
that miracles exist
and ultimately,
God exists.
I love that.
Thank you so much
for your time, Muhammad.
We really appreciate you.
It's great to see you again.
Likewise.
Goodbye, man.
Always welcome.
Yeah, it means a lot to us.
Really appreciate it.
Guys,
we just wrapped up.
We just wrapped up
with one of the richest men
in Dubai, Muhammad Bugatti.
We got to see
the Bugatti residences
before it comes
this right here.
But next year,
we may have to do
another video,
run it back,
but like, subscribe
for amazing content
every week.
Guys, I'm bringing you guys
the billionaires
from every part of the world
here on this channel, man.
Go down,
click the link
in the description
of this video
to join the number one
community for business owners
and entrepreneurs
in today's world
where you get direct access
to billionaire entrepreneurs
that I interview,
the eight-figure,
the nine-figure,
the ten-figure business owners
that I interview
on this channel.
You get to speak directly
in the description
and I'll see you on the inside.
That being said,
see you in the next video.